[{"answer": "Shelter. my friend adapted by my friend March 2008 4", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I have no strength to go", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What do you want", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I have done nothing wrong. Master Reed", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Please", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I shall be killed", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'll remember how you thrust me back into the Red Room and locked me there to my dying day. Even when you knew it was haunted and I begged to be let out. People think you are good but you are bad and har", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Deceit is not my fault", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Children must be corrected for their faults", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "But you are passionate", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "You're such a queer, solitary little thing. If only you could make yourself more appealing. Perhaps if you tried smiling from time to time, people would find you more pleasant", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't dislike you Mis", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You're not allowed to speak to me. I must be shunned", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He said I was a liar", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Why ever not", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Can he not do God's work here", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I don't have any talent to make my way in life. I should be always at fault. But God is my friend. He loves me", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He is saving me", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Who", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh you mean Miss Varen", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Miss that place", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Who is Mr that place", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh you mean Miss Varen", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Why, the owner of that place", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Whose house is that", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Do you know Mr that place", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I have to change", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "But all my dresses are the same", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "my frien", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Where did you get your copies", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "That head I now see on your shoulders", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Now you stick a knife under my EAR", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Just s", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What in the name of all the elves in that place have you done with me", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Light the lamp at your peril", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.  Goo", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You said I should go", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "We shall have music", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Beauty? Why there's nothing new to be said. I give you back male beauty. Mamma, what's your idea of male beauty", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You cursed me", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "My life has been cursed", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "that place is a pleasant place in summer, isn't it", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yes, but it can't be helped. I soon hope to be a bridegroom", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Because of your bride", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "But you will have", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Is this my pale elf? This sunny faced girl with the radiant eyes", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Soon to be my friend", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Sir", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I do", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "I would", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "It would be to obey you. I care for myself. my friend adapted by my friend March 2008 100", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "That is correct. my friend adapted by my friend March 2008 106", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Why this refusal? It makes no sense", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " I'd kill you? I am killing you? Your words are violent, unfeminine and untrue", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "And the worst of it is, I'm in danger of loving you too well for this, and making too much of you", "docId": "Jane-Eyre.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Very. But you always were, you know", "qsentId": 58}]